http://www.arborlawnumc.org/privacy-policy

I'm New
Privacy PolicyIt is Arborlawn United Methodist Church’s (UMC) policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to https://www.arborlawnumc.org (hereinafter, "us", "we", or "https://www.arborlawnumc.org"). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the Website. We have adopted this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms and conditions posted on our Website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.Website VisitorsLike most website operators, Arborlawn UMC collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Arborlawn UMC's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Arborlawn UMC's visitors use its website. From time to time, Arborlawn UMC may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.Arborlawn UMC also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on https://www.arborlawnumc.org blog posts. Arborlawn UMC only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.Gathering of Personally-Identifying InformationCertain visitors to Arborlawn UMC's websites choose to interact with Arborlawn UMC in ways that require Arborlawn UMC to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Arborlawn UMC gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a blog at https://www.arborlawnumc.org to provide a username and email address.SecurityThe security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. AdvertisementsAds appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Arborlawn UMC and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. Links To External SitesOur Service may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and terms and conditions of every site you visit.We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites, products or services.Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying InformationArborlawn UMC discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Arborlawn UMC's behalf or to provide services available at Arborlawn UMC's website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Arborlawn UMC's website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Arborlawn UMC will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Arborlawn UMC discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Arborlawn UMC believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Arborlawn UMC, third parties or the public at large.If you are a registered user of https://www.arborlawnumc.org and have supplied your email address, Arborlawn UMC may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Arborlawn UMC and our products. We primarily use our blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Arborlawn UMC takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.Aggregated StatisticsArborlawn UMC may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. Arborlawn UMC may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Arborlawn UMC does not disclose your personally-identifying information. CookiesTo enrich and perfect your online experience, Arborlawn UMC uses "Cookies", similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer.A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Arborlawn UMC uses cookies to help Arborlawn UMC identify and track visitors, their usage of https://www.arborlawnumc.org, and their website access preferences. Arborlawn UMC visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Arborlawn UMC's websites, with the drawback that certain features of Arborlawn UMC's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to Arborlawn UMC's use of cookies.Privacy Policy ChangesAlthough most changes are likely to be minor, Arborlawn UMC may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Arborlawn UMC's sole discretion. Arborlawn UMC encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change
Arborlawn Connect
Bulletin Board
Subscribe to news
Give Online
CONTACT:5001 Briarhaven RoadFort Worth, Tx 76109817.731.0701CONNECT:
STAFF PORTAL
